Guide to the Walter Freeman, Class of 1916, Yale College, Photograph Albums Documenting Life at Yale
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Volumes I and II
  - Page 71
    - 364. Blossom, Quinby, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - 365. Omega Lambda Chi [parade], 1913 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - 366. [baseball] game, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - 367. Blake, Leiper, Wentworth, Guenther [sailing] (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Page 72
    - 368. Tap day, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - 369. Watrous (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - 370. 1913 [shooting] (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - 371. Vaughn, Hunter, Osborn, Reilly, Harpham - 1914 [baseball] (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - 372. Johnstone, 1913 [pole vault] (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - 373. [Baseball] (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Page 73
    - 374. [Inside Old Campus] (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - 375. [March in the Berkeley Oval] (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - 376. Middlebrook safe at third - Tufts game, 1913 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - 377. W.A. Hunter, 1915S (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - 378. Legare sliding to third - Yale-Princeton game, 1913 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Page 74
    - 379. News vs. Heelers, 1913 - Slimmon slides into Royce (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - 380. Omega Lambda Chi, 1913 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - 381. News vs. Heelers - Slimmon, Coley - 1913 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - 382. Yale at Georgetown [baseball] (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - 383. Vaughn, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - 384. Swihart, 1914 [baseball] (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Page 75
    - 385. Wagoner [pole vault] (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - 386. Mack (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - 387. [Pole vault] (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - 388. [Track] (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - 389. Roos (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - 390. Queal, Knapp (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Page 76
    - 391. Cowles, Ravell [Track] (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - 392. Poucher (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - 393. [Pole vault] (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - 394. Mid-Cornell [track] (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - 395. Roos (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - 396. Mack, Wagoner (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - 397, Wagoner, Mack (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - 398. Shedden, Smith (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Page 77
    - 399. Hovey, 1915 [baseball] (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - 400. Literary window in Library (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - 401. Omega Lambda Chi, 1913 - Nuns caused a row in New Haven (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - 402. Pickett, 1913 [Discus] (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - 403. Oler, 1913 [high jump] (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - 404. Hammer throwers, 1913 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Page 78
    - 405. Washburn, Fagan - 1914 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - 406. Sophomore baseball, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - 407. New Haven Green, 1914 [from Old Campus] (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - 408. Grant, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - 409. Yale Dramat, movies 1915 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Page 79
    - 410. Legore makes 25 yards, 1914 [football] (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - 411. Tener, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - 412. Harvard Game, 1914 [football] (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - 413. Taft reception, 1913 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - 414. [Football] (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - 415. 1915 Record Board (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Page 80
    - 416. Tittman (wounded 1918), Guernsey, Sproul, Hampton, Vaughn - 1914 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - 417. 1913 [football] (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - 418. 1914 [football] (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - 419. Omega Lambda Chi, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Page 81
    - 420. Talbot Field, Bull - on old Yale Field (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - 421. Football, 1915 [on campus] (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - 422. Construction of Osborn Lab, 1913 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - 423. Fire, 1913 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - 424. Bromeisler Y 1914 and Catlin (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Page 82
    - 425. Harvard Game, 1914 [football] (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - 426. Harvard Game, 1914 [football] (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - 427. Lyman Y 1913 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - 428. Frank, 1913 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - 429. Omega Lambda Chi, 1913 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Page 83
    - 430. Excavating the Bowl (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - 431. Waiting for a report by Daily News of Yale-Princeton Game at Princeton (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - 432. Excavating the Bowl (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - 433. The Sophomore Fence, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Page 84
    - 434. Football men at baseball game after spring practice, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - 435. Psi Upsilon on Calcium Light Night, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - 436. Bunker, Ranson, Sanderson, Lane - Zeta Psi (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - 437. Whiffenpoof Funeral at Yale-Brown Game, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Page 85
    - 438. Allen, Jones, Hyde, Titus, Robinson, White, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - 439. Whiffenpoof funeral, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - 440. 1914 Guernsey [with ball], Scovil (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - 441. Omega Lambda Chi - 1915 - Whiffenpoofs vs. Hogans (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Page 86
    - 442. Omega Lambda Chi - 1915 - Note Lusitania Headline Miller, Clarke, Wood, Welch, Boardman (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - 443. Hillhouse Avenue, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - 444. Omega Lambda Chi, 1915 - Crocker and Porter take a scene from Chin Chin (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - 445. News Heelers, 1912 - Smith, Brown, Freeman (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Page 87
    - 446. April 1914 [Taft] (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - 447. Jan. 1914 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - 448-49. [Taft reception at railroad station] (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - 450. [Parade] (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Page 88
    - 451. [Taft reception at railroad station] (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - 452. Crew off to Gales Ferry (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - 453. The Speech (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - 454. Lined up [corner of Chapel and College Streets] (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - 455. Second Regiment band (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - 456. [Parade] (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Page 89
    - 457. Jepson [at Newberry Organ] (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - 458. Big Snow, 1914 [Elm Street in front of Oval] (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - 459. Linonian and Brothers Library (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - 460. Cambridge (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - 461. 1913 Lit. Board - Meeker (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - 462. Biology (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - 463. [Studying] (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - 464. Biology (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - 465. [A Library] (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Page 90
    - 466. Goodwin [at desk] 1914 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - 467. [Large crowd in a gallery (?)] (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - 468. Byers Hall [pool tables] (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - 469. Orchestra, 1913 [boarding trolley] (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - 470. [Playing pool] (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - 471. Quinby (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - 472. [Inside a dining hall] (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - 473. Duplicate of picture 459 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - 474. [At a linotype] (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Page 91
    - 475. [Feeding a squirrel] (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - 476. Yale Babylonian Museum, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - 477. Looking south east from Wright (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - 478. 1913 [football] (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - 479. Yale-Brown, 1913 [spectators] (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Page 92
    - 480. February, 1916 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - 481. F.V. Burgess (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - 482. Alumni Day, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - 483. Beers-Phelps, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - 484. Osborn, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - 485. [Football] (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Page 93
    - 486. Looking east on Elm Street (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - 487. Battell (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - 488. Freshmen Debaters, 1913 -Bolton, Blake, Beach, Lorimer, Cary, Dudley, McChesney (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - 489. Song and Bull session, 1913 - Jones, Eastman, Hyde, Sutherland, Phenix, Willard, Proctor (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - 490. [Football practice] (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - 491. Crocker, Porter, Bastwick, Nellier, Allen,Williams, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Page 94
    - 492. L. Miller, 1916 [rolling hoop down College Street] (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - 493. Circus, 1914 [corner of Elm and College Streets] (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - 494. Campus south from Durfee (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - 495. Ricketts under fire, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Page 95-96 MISSING
  - Page 97
    - 496. Diggs 1913S, 1913 [broad jump] (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - 497. Start of 440, 1913 Fall (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - 498. Grubb on West Rock, 1912 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - 499. 1914 [baseball] (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - 500. [Baseball player] (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - 501. Yale-Princeton [baseball] at New York, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Page 98
    - 502. Taft reception, 1913 - cheerleaders (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - 503. Quinby, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - 504. Crocker, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - 505. Osborn out [baseball], 1913 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - 506. Everard, Crawford - Faculty - P.B.K., 1913 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - 507. Taft [walking down street] reception (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - 508. Fall [track] meet, 1913-- Treadway (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Volume III
  - Page 1
    - 509. At Leland Stanford - the start of push ball (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - 510. University of Illinois (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - 511. Southern California University (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - 512. Cairolin, J.R. Mott (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - 513. [4-legged race] (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - 514. [Large group of young men] (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Page 2
    - 515. Geologist class examining Branford (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - 516. Dramat. Movie play, May 1913 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - 517. Mory's Association (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - 518. Taking the winning shell to be freighted to Gales Ferry, 1914 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - 519. Omega Lambda Chi - Photographers on every post, 1913 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - 520. The Green from the Taft Hotel (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - 521. Baseball on the Sheff campus (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - 522. [walking south past Connecticut Hall] (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - 523. [Entering gate (full dress) - see picture 564] (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Page 3
    - 524. Rustic scenes at Leland Stanford (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - 525. 1914 in the oval as Juniors (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - 526. 1916 as Sophomores - Heeley, Bassett, Eckmann, Taylor, Ricketts, Bunker, Britingham, Robinson, Cady, Geary, Nure, Newton (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - 527. Individual scraps at Amherst (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - 529. Burges, 1916 - Macdonald, 1917 - York, 1917 [hockey] (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - 530. Duplicate of picture 527 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - 531. [Group running] (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Page 4
    - 532. University of Southern California-- watching the rush (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - 533. Visiting the library - Alumni University day, 1914 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - 534. Moonlight [looking south east] (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - 535. Duplicate of picture 533 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - 536. [Ladies at a garden party] (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - 537. [Baseball in Quadrangle] (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Page 5
    - 538. Hillhouse tennis courts (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - 539. Handball practice at Izzy Winter's Gym, 1915 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - 540. Battery drill at Leland Stanford (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - 541. Afternoon basketball in gym, 1915 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - 542. [Parade] (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - 543. [exercises in the gym] (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Page 6
    - 544. [Hockey] Driscoll 1915S, Dickey Y 1916, Heron Y 1914S (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - 545. 1914 seniors playing on the campus (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - 546. Omega Lambda Chi baseball game (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - 547. Whiffenpoof celebration, 1913 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - 548. Good hunting in Durfee [holding string of mice] - Gamble, An. Phillips, Jr. (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - 549. [Game - Omega Lambda Chi (?)] (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - 550. 1913 Seniors in cap and gown (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - 551. Surveying the Hillhouse property (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Page 7
    - 552. Platform rush at Williams (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - 553. Nickerson 1915S [fencing] (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - 554. Soccer with Harvard on Pratt field (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - 555. [hockey game] (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - 556. [hockey player] (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - 557. A soccer scrimmage with Haverford (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Page 8
    - 558. Samuels at a handstand on the bars (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - 559. Senior Amusements - Cooney, Marting (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - 560. Omega Lambda Chi sports - Patterson, Lynch, Hazard (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - 561. [Track] - ??, McKenzie (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - 562. [Broad jump] (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - 563. [Hockey] (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Page 9
    - 564. Prom patrons (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - 565. Cheering the crew off for the ferry, 1914 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - 566. [Taft] (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - 567. [Taft] (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - 568. Seeing the crew off for the ferry, 1914 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - 569. Me and Taft (W.J. Freeman) (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - 570. [Mr. and Mrs. Taft] (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - 571. Notables at Yale-Princeton Game, 1913 -Hadley, Mrs. Hadley, Know, Taft, Mrs. Taft (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - 572. 1913 [in caps and gowns] (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - 573. After the corporation meeting [Taft] (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - 574. Mrs. Taft (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Page 10
    - 575. Phelps archway (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - 576. Yale hope mission clearing snow (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - 577. [Cat watching squirrel] (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - 578. Coasting at girls school in Switzerland (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - 579. [Cat watching squirrel] (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - 580. Peter's reward [squirrel in arm] (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - 581. 1915 in a snow battle (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - 582. Veaser, Grubb, Hyde, Goodwin, Abel [in a snowball fight] (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - 583. Whiffenpoofs at 1913 Brown Game (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Page 11
    - 584. Commons during mealtime (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - 585. Diabolo on skates (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - 586. Sight of the Bowl [bare] (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - 587. Whiffenpoofs (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - 588. Upper hall in New Sloane Laboratory (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - 589. Signs of spring - 16 whole panes (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - 590. The then new baseball cage, 1913 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Page 12
    - 591. Elm Street - What chance has a pedestrian? (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - 592. Sunday service in Woolsey (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - 593. The new St. Elmo (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - 594. Working on the new Osborne lab (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Page 13
    - 595. Connecticut Foot guards - Query Head guards (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - 596. Omega Lambda Chi parade, 1918 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - 597. Parade of --the finest (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - 598. Cheering the crew off, 1913 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - 599-600. [Parade] (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - 601. [Parade - Taft's?] (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Page 14
    - 602. 1914 Senior Party on to Mamauguin (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - 603. R.I.P. (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - 604. Chess room (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - 605. Group walking along a street (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - 606-07. Funny stuff at Princeton (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - 608. In Wright Court (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - 609. In Wright Court (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - 610. Oak Street Boys Club (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Page 15
    - 611. G.W. Goodwin (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - 612. W.J. Freeman (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - 613. A.W. Harrison (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - 614. [Statue - Nathan Hale] (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - 615. E.D. Thomas (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - 616. [Portrait of ?] (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Page 16
    - 617. Library group from Phelps Tower (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - 618. Unidentified (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - 619. Alumni Hall reproduction in Bones [beginnings of Weir Hall] (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - 620. Hillhouse property and Sloane Lab (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - 621. Old campus looking south (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - 622. [Construction of Wright Hall] (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - 623. [View towards hills] (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - 624. [Hadley] (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Page 17
    - 625. Starting the new armory at Illinois (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - 626. Starting the new St. Anthony (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - 627. A mouse cornered - Pernns, Robinson, Gee, Gaillard, Johnson (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - 628. [Man on horseback in lots of water] (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - 629. [Man carving a cross] (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - 630. [construction] (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - 631. [Rainy day - a corner - news boys] (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Page 18
    - 632. CCNY terrace (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - 633. Cairo University (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - 634. CCNY Library (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - 635. City College of New York (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - 636. [Looking northwest towards Wright - men with suitcases] (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - 637. [Men working on a hill] (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - 638. [Group of musicians - Banjo, Guitar, Singers] (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Page 19
    - 639. Tap day on Sheff Campus - giving elections to Kopper Kettle Club, 1913 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - 640. Rush scenes at Amherst (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - 641. "Charlie Chaplin" on campus (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - 642. 1917 as Sophomores (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - 643. Senior party bound for Momauguin (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - 644. [Snow ball fight] (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - 645. [Baseball on Campus] (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - 646. [Snow ball fight] (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Page 20
    - 647. Wisconsin bonfire (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - 648. War relics at Branford (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - 649. On the Wye at Oxford (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - 650. Ostend, Belgium (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - 651. On the Wye at Oxford (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - 652. [Race or tug of war on a river or lake] (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - 653. On the Wye at Oxford (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - 654. [Race or tug of war on a river or lake] (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Page 21
    - 655. Amherst Library (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - 656. McGesney at Art School door (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - 657. C.C.N.Y. (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - 658. Campus at Night (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - 659. Library (old) Group (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - 660. Green from Taft Hotel (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - 661. Baseball (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Page 22
    - 662. Princeton (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - 663. From below the chapel clock (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - 664. Capt - H. Bartlett's Lithograph --Yale College (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - 665. [Group of professors, deans, etc. on speakers platform - Dwight] (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - 666. Gunners at the end of the race [cameramen at track meet] (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - 667. Finishing touches on Osborne Lab [under construction] (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - 668. Old Elm upturned by ice storm, 1915 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - 669. Taking Dramat. movie, 1913 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Page 23
    - 670. Cosmopolitan Club (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - 671. Orchestra, 1912-13 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - 672. 1915 Sophomores snowballing (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - 673. Oval through Lampson Arch (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - 674. University of Pennsylvania Triangle (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - 675. Choir rehearsal (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Page 24
    - 676. Byers Hall (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - 677. Van-Sheff and Memorial Halls (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - 678. Old Library (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - 679. Phelps Gateway (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - 680. Alumni visiting Peabody, 1914 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - 681. [Center Church in snow] (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Page 25
    - 682. Hopkins Grammar School (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - 683. Signs of Spring - signs appear (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - 684. Rear of Osborne Lab (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - 685. [Athletic field of a school] (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - 686. Princeton campus (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - 687-88. [Shore house ?] (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - 689. Campus from Dwight (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Page 26
    - 690. Princeton (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - 691. Miller Gateway (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - 692. Result of ice storm (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - 693. [Old building in snow] (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - 694. Phelps through Dwight (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - 695. Princeton (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Page 27
    - 696. Gore Hall, Harvard (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - 697. [Shore house? - Duplicate of picture 688] (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - 698. Lehigh baseball team crossing campus (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - 699. [Sitting on porch of Gales ferry Post Office] (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - 700. Princeton (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - 701. Leete-Oliver Memorial Lab (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - 702. The senior corner of the campus (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - 703. [Wright Hall] (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - 704. [Campus building?] (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Page 28
    - 705. Lampson Lions plus hats (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - 706. [A church] (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - 707. Noah Porter Gateway (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - 708. Princeton (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - 709. White, Linehart, Clark (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - 710. Brown University Campus (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - 711. Osborne Lab entrance (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Page 29
    - 712. Addition to Bones [Old Alumni Towers] (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - 713. Coe testing fliers, 1912 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - 714. Locks at Gatum (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - 715. [Building under construction] (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - 716. George Adee Boathouse (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - 717. Boarding the car [trolley] at Easter (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - 718. Ammonia pump at the Plant (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - 719. Commons behind the scenes (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - 720. Slugger-- Bill Ingersall (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Page 30
    - 721. Building Saint Anthony Hall (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - 722. Harvard Lampoon Building (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - 723. Entrances to the Bowl [under construction] (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - 724. Pouring Concrete into retaining wall [Bowl ?] (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - 725. Tree surgery [Elm Street next to Hendrie Hall] (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - 726. Part of the retaining wall of the Bowl finished (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - 727. A close view of Saint Anthony operations[under construction] (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Page 31
    - 728. Ransom Brothers on the Fence (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - 729. Library and Woolsey Statue [in snow] (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - 730. Alumni University Day, Feb. 22, 1913 (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - 731. [Unidentified building] (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - 732. Sunday service at Battell (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - 734. Oval after Branford (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - 735. Alumni visiting Sheff (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Page 32
    - 736. Harvard Yard (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - 737. Harvard Elm (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - 738. Unidentified (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - 739. Southern California University (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - 740. Building Saint Anthony Hall, 1913 (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - 742. West River Monument (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - 743. Wright Gateway (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - 744. Wright Hall from Phelps (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Page 33
    - 745. Inside Center Church railing (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - 746. Center Church pillars (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - 747. 1914 going to class (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - 748. [Unidentified University] (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - 749. Snow buntings by Osborn (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - 750. Sophomore baseball (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Page 34
    - 751. Brown University (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - 752. Osborne Lab Tower (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - 753. [Sloane Lab] (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - 754. Duplicate of picture 618? (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - 755. College and Chapel Streets (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - 756. Battell, Farnam, Lawrance, Phelps - Sophomore Row (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - 757. Old Library through Phelps (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - 758. Harvard [Lampoon Building Site] (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Page 35
    - 759. Night Scene [Old Campus] (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - 760. Library and Dwight (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - 761. Campus from Connecticut Hall (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - 762. Taft Corner [inside Old Campus] (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - 763. [Phelps] (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - 764. [Memorial Plaque to Rev. Noah Porter] (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - 765. Yale hope mission workshop (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Page 36
    - 766. Wright Hall (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - 767. Copy of Kings College Library, Cambridge [Dwight] (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - 768. Yale Observatory on Prospect Hill (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - 769. Prom patrons, 1914 (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - 770. WOPs clearing snow (Box 2, Folder 65)